I drove cross-country in a car like this.
我曾经开着一辆这样的车横越国家.
Did it make it?
那辆车做到了吗?
Eventually.
最后还是做到了.
We started in Boston.
我们从波士顿出发.
Then we went to Ohio to visit some relatives.
然后去俄亥俄(Ohio)拜访了几个亲戚.
Then out west.
然后就一直往西开.
What was that like?
西部是什么样子?
Fantastic. Everything's bigger.
美不胜收. 所有东西都比这里的大.
The mountains are higher.
山更高.
The canyons are deeper.
峡谷更深.
The land goes on and on.
土地无边无际.
Where did you stay?
你们住在哪儿?
We camped.
我们宿营.
Except for one week we stayed with a family in Butte,Montana.
除了有一个星期我们是和一家人住在一起的 在蒙大拿洲(Montana)比尤特市(Butte).
More relatives?
又是亲戚?
No, the car broke down in front of their house.
No, 车在他们的房子前面坏掉了.
You know what else was great about camping?
你知道宿营还有什么别的好处吗?
What?
什么?
It was very quiet.
非常安静.
Yeah,well...
Shall we put on some music?
我们要不要来点音乐?
Yes!
Much better!
现在好多了!